We have talked in the previous video about printing the link, at least in reverse order, and we see
that we have used that recursion now in order to make this very simple.
I will demonstrate the recursion in a different way.
So you see guys that in the method here we print reversely and we are making use of recursion and print,
reversely and passing.
And then next.
How does this means of words?
We have this this link unless we start by.
Brent, reversely, this is the method that we are going to execute.
And that if had equal equal to none, no, it is not equal to now, so we are not going to secure the
return.
We will print recursively.
We are going to bear a call the next one, which at the head, the next the head, the next we are putting
the reference, which is 2024.
So we are calling the method again, print recursively and we are passing the address 2024.
OK, now.
This method, Brent, recursively, we'll start executing if had equal equal to no, no, it will not
return, it will execute Brent recursively head dot next and it will not execute print.
This is the basics of recursion.
So please, guys, if you don't understand the the recursion, how it works, please go to the Karajan
section and watch the videos now.
Print Richter reversely it will be executed and we are calling print recursively, reversely the method
and passing three thousand twenty four.
This is the end of that, or three thousand forty.
It's not a big deal.
I'm giving you that the basics of and the content.
Void, Brent, recursively, I'm calling this method, I'm passing, passing through their arguments.
The index and the reference of the last known, which is 38, 24 or 40 if had equal equal to null return
and then print recursively the next note?
OK, so this had equal equal to null the because the next node print recursively had had equal to next.
And recall the print recursive reversely method and it were returned because had now equal to null.
Again, now this now would be a return and printing their one one nine, so it will execute the last
print f had of date.
And then this will be executing reversely by printing after the head of state.
So it starts from the last by printing that last as executing the Leicester statement and then going
backward to continue executing the print f of had the data or the data of they're not.
OK.